http://www.pwmall.com/privacy-policy

Low Prices
Fast Shipping!
SINCE 1991
Ag Spraying Equipment, Hoses,Pressure Washers, Sewer Jetters,Water Pumps & More
Auto & Truck Detailing
(20)
Clamps
(33)
Coupling
& Quick Disconnects
(184)
Facility Cleaning & Maintenance
(120)
Filters & Strainers
(76)
Fittings - Brass, Nylon, Polypropylene & Steel
(937)
Gauges
(61)
Hose & Tubing
(416)
Hose Reels & Hangers
(25)
Hydraulic Cylinders & Accessories
(12)
Hydro Excavation
(85)
LP-Gas, Nat Gas, RV's & Campers
(89)
Pressure Washer
(802)
Pumps
(529)
Repair Kits & Parts
(1172)
Sewer Cleaning
(337)
Soft Wash Units & Accessories
(120)
Sprayers, Accessories & Parts
(560)
Swivels
(22)
Tools
(69)
Valves
(259)
Warning & Work Lights
(12)
Brands
Annovi Reverberi - AR North America
BAND-IT-IDEX, Inc.
BE Pressure Supply
Beckett, R.W. Corp.
Breco
View all
Newsletter
Sign up for our newsletter:
Wait...
Information Collection and Use
PRI Industries, Inc. (pwmall) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. PRI Industries, Inc. (pwmall) collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
No Release of Information to Third Parties
Personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information, such as approving your credit card number for a purchase or entering information for shipping purposes or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.
Orders
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
Cookies
We use cookies in 2 ways.
Session ID
Our StoreFront shopping system uses a "session ID" to manage each shoppers order. The session ID is a "non-persistent" cookie meaning that it is never saved to your computers hard drive but is only cached in the browsers memory for twenty minutes or until the browser is closed.
To complete your shopping process your browser must be set to accept the session ID. The shopping process requires the Session ID in order for it to work. This will enable us to accurately track and record your order.
Order Cookie
This order cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. The cookie is set when a customer goes from the Order Page to the Finalize My Order Page. If you stop before this point, there is no cookie. If you go to the last page, but then abandon the order, it will remain for 24 hours, then terminate unless the order process is continued. Once the user completes the order process, it will remain for one year, during which they can come back and reorder. Each time the user orders, the cookie is updated to show the last order. Only the last order can be retrieved.
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
Log Files
We use internal Web Service on our web site to track information about the visits to our web site. For example, they compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web site, and what browsers & platforms those requests use. Also, Netscape collects information on what search engines and keyword where used to find our site and how our site was located or linked. These aggregated statistics are provided to us to use internally, but again, the statistics contain no personal information.
Our computer is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors.
Sharing
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we PRI Industries, Inc. (pwmall) are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at support@pwmall.com
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
power equipment and supply
BRANDS
SHIPPING QUOTE
ABOUT
GENERAL INFORMATION
CONTACT US
My Account
Order Status
Help
Shopping Cart
Login
Copyright © 2020 PWMall.com. All Rights Reserved.
877-979-6255
Powered by nopCommerce
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.
OK
Learn more
